All right, first years, come introduce yourselves.
Yes, sir!
Hi, my name is Koshi Sugawara, and I'm a setter, and I come from Nagamushi.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I... I'm Asi Azumane, and I play left-sided Sekodai.
I'm a pleasure to meet you, too.
Oh, crap.
My name is Daiichi Sawamura. I'm from Azumadate.
I play left, too. I saw Karasuno play at Nationals.
That's why I chose this school. Looking forward to playing with you.
Oh, yeah? Well, there you go. I like your enthusiasm.
Then why don't we aim for Nationals this year?
Yes, sir!
I'm Tashiro, the team captain, and I cannot wait to work with you guys.
You kids have fun now. I'll drop by later.
See ya. All right, let's get to practicing.
Okay!
So I guess the guy who just walked out is our advisor?
Is there, like, a coach on the way or something?
There's no coach.
Wait, wasn't that Kurokawa from Issa Middle School?
So you know him?
I played against him. His attacks were so incredible.
Defense, too.
Oh!
Really? That's so cool!
We're finally here at the famous Karasuno!
Boy, you know.
Okay.
Thank you.
Aw.
Hey, Kurokawa, could you maybe give me some pointers on my receives?
The moment I see the opponent hit the ball, I just get ready for it.
Uh, okay.
Time to wrap up!
Yes, sir!
Hey, the tournament is coming up. Shouldn't we have some practice matches?
They said that ever since Coach Yukai left, our relationships with other schools have been slowly falling apart.
Yeah, I heard there was a school they were practicing with right before we got here. And now even those guys have turned us down.
Huh? Why's that?
They don't see the point wasting any of their time working with us.
I knew Kurasuna wasn't the team it used to be.
But I thought if we practiced hard enough, we could bring it back to its former greatness.
It didn't feel like a hopeless situation, nor was there any huge conflict.
However, there was still a lingering fear that we were losing our way.
Um, so, would you guys mind if I practiced a little more? I'll lock up afterwards.
Uh, me too, if that's cool.
Me three! I'll go tell the advisor.
Uh, sure.
We can't go on like this. Nationals aren't far away.
Oh, you sound like a teacher.
Yeah, or a dad. Are you sure you're just a first year?
If we keep learning, then we'll keep getting better.
Yeah!
The Spiker's form shows the ball's corpse.
Hey, you're not supposed to catch it.
I'm sorry!
We'll find ways to learn and grow.
We just have to keep our chins up and work hard at improving.
Tomorrow's the qualifying tournament for Nationals.
You only get one shot, boys.
Yes, sir!
Winning Nationals is our only goal!
Dude, I've been thinking, maybe we should be setting our goals as something that we actually have a chance of achieving.
Huh?
You can lose a lot of your self-confidence if you try setting the bar too high, and nobody wants that, right?
Whoa! You okay, man?
Up until now, you've always given me a dirty look or just ignored me whenever I said we were going to Nationals.
But not now.
Now you're finally biting back!
I love it!
You have any idea why that makes me so happy?
Uh, not really.
Maybe we aren't on the same page as far as goals go, but we've come a long way and we get along really well now.
Plus, we all have this burning desire to win the next game, right, guys?
So let's go win!
Yeah!
Ha-ha!
And then, the Miyagi Prefecture Prelims.
We lost in the second round.
And our third years retired from club activities.
I guess that means our crows have fallen.
Damn, maybe we realized the value of teamwork too late.
It's true.
Chance really does favor the prepared.
That's where we screwed up.
I feel like we've hit rock bottom.
Karasuno might never come back from this slump.
Or if we do, it might be in the distant future.
Who knows?
Even so, if you get another chance, then take it!
Now, now is our chance, and we're gonna take it!
They haven't been guarding against Hinata's blocks until recently, so I can tell it's getting under their skin.
Even if it's only a small crack in their armor, it'll prove to be useful for us in the end.
It's a chance, Ball!
Damn it!
All right, we finally took the lead from them.
Now, don't give it back!
Gatsuki!
I'm a second too late!
They're definitely taking notice of Hinata now.
It can't be ignored.
That's gonna be a straight!
Leave this to me!
Nice kill!
We can't let Hinata have all the fun, right?
Hey, Kageyama!
Nice receive!
Thanks!
This one's got a strong serve.
Let's nip it in the bud!
Yeah!
Nishidara!
Sorry, that's long!
Hold your ground, Goshiki.
Kurosuno Setter is in the back row, so they aren't gonna dump.
Just watch closely.
What?
He's already here?
Shit!
It's this far into the game, and their moves are still so sharp.
These guys are machines!
It doesn't matter how many times they've practiced it before, that move is always gonna be tough
to pull off.
You're in, Specs!
About time!
I thought they'd never take number 10 out.
Suki!
Don't let Hinata beat you!
Huh?
Yeah, like there's any comparison.
Kageyama.
Yeah?
You got this.
Right.
I can do this.
What about you, Tsukishima?
Well, I worked a bit with Akashi.
This jerk's been practicing with Vukorodani Setter?
Makes me kinda jealous.
Ginger!
Come sit down.
Take any chance you can to rest.
Conserve your energy.
Okay.
I don't wanna lose to Hinata either.
This time, I'm gonna prove myself worthy.
Give us a good serve, Tanashi!
Hey, wait.
Isn't he a little further back than usual?
Your serve could be a valuable weapon.
Straight.
Just hit it straight.
Toward Ushiwaka.
Yes, we broke through.
Keep it up.
Go ski!
Got it!
Make him follow.
A three-man block!
Don't underestimate me.
I'll get through!
One touch!
Not on my watch now!
Nice cover!
A time differential attack?
That's right.
You're not the only one who learned some new tricks during training camp.
Hinata.
Yeah!
Whoa!
The rest of them broke through!
Damn, that guy in the glasses has some guts.
God damn it!
Nice!
You can't move!
You show off!
You're completely dropping your elbows!
If you lazy nitwits were using proper form, then your spikes would break through everything!
You've all got these huge hulking bodies, so you have to be more, uh, more, more, more, more...
Dineric!
Yeah!
It's true, their defense is good, and they're constantly evolving it, but still, it's just a stopgap measure.
However, there is no such thing as the perfect defense.
Unleash the beast, Hanashi!
And head next!
Front!
On it!
I tried to comedy!
At next!
Front!
On it!
Damn it!
Ushiwaka makes it look so easy!
Yeah, but he's hit so many of these by now.
His legs have got to be getting tired.
Uh-huh.
If we just hang on, even someone like Ushiwaka will run out of steam.
You got this, Asahi!
Got it!
He's off!
Yeah! So gay!
Oh my god, my heart just skipped a beat!
Can't believe he pulled that off!
We're at set point, right?
It's their first five-set match,
and it's against a team that regularly makes it to Nationals.
From the fourth set on, this is unexplored territory for our Crows.
Since the game started, number nines had to compensate for Shorty's insane attacks.
Plus, make sure he gets just the right kind of sets.
Precision is also expected out of him.
Probably more so than anyone else on that team.
All while being under a lot of pressure to block our advances.
Not to mention, he also handles the ball more than any single player.
I'm thinking he'll be the first one to reach his limit.
That's my fault!
You creep me out when you apologize.
I don't accept it.
What?
Much better.
Daichi, serve us something sweet!
The front!
Ushiwaka!
Damn it!
Hey, wait, do you think Shira Torizawa has a second bench server?
It wouldn't surprise me.
I'm sure their bench has just about everything.
Hang in there, you guys.
Please don't bring this into a deuce.
Let's do this!
A jump float, serve?
Sorry!
They picked it up!
There's Ushiwaka!
Ushiwaka!
On my call, and now!
No way!
When you're defending one part of the court,
another area will always be vulnerable.
If they're gathered in the back,
then naturally,
it leaves the front
wide open.
They totally saw it.
We left a huge space open.
Yeah, that's true, but still,
I thought Kageyama would have been able to pick that up.
His fatigue must be getting to him.
Oh, is the tired Widow Shatter
going to have to deal a deuce of despair?
Nothing you could do
would bring me despair.
It would only be
if I wasn't able to play volleyball.
You're all just a bunch of
jerky
jerkheads.
Come on!
Let's go!
Our defense is fine as is.
Great job on those one touches.
Right!
Kageyama, you good?
Yeah, of course.
If you're worn out,
I'm ready to switch any time.
I said I'm fine!
Daichi!
It's coming in high.
Yes!
Well, that puts him back at set point again.
It's a deuce again.
It's okay!
We can still take it!
Now of all times,
it's his turn to serve again!
Bring it!
Ladies and gentlemen,
Roshi Rolga!
Of course they would get
a net at a time like this!
Oh no!
Now they have match point!
If they get another point,
it's over.
One more point!
Come on, guys!
Can't get there?
Come on!
Noia!
That damn demon served!
It's a chance ball!
No way!
God damn it!
It's a chance!
They held on all the way through match point!
All right!
Kageyama, do you mind not running into me, please?
Maybe you should learn from Hinata.
Jump up, not across.
Huh?
That was nothing, you brain-dead piece of wimpy sissy crap!
You just don't have the training to take it!
You guys need to chill out!
This is taking years off my life.
Anybody have an antacid?
Hey!
Stop being so melodramatic.
This ain't nothing.
Huh?
Says the guy who had a conniption when Shira Torizawa had that chance ball.
This ain't nothing.
Huh?
Not compared to back when they were still fresh in everyone's minds as a championship school.
But couldn't live up to the legacy.
You better get your grip together, Karasuno!
Huh?
Who was that?
Not sure.
That old fart is still coming to our matches, I see.
Well, we should live up to his expectations then.
Now go!
My most annoying opponent.
Is it an enemy or a blocker?
It's this guy.
Yeah!
Okay!
Now make sure they hear us!
Now go!
Go!
Kurasu no!
Push it!
Go!
Kurasu no!
Push it!
I'll hit any sucky-ass sets you send my way!
The only sucky-ass thing around here is you!
Got it!
If they're putting in Sugawara as a pinched server right now, that means they're planning on keeping Kageyama in there until the end of the set.
Well, it would do us more harm than good to change setters at such a critical point.
Your time to shine, Suga!
Rayon, go front!
Nice receipt!
Your beautiful form is slowly falling apart!
That's hell!
Kageyama could've let the left side handle that, but I can tell he really likes to control the flow of the game.
I think it's called a silent boast.
No matter how tired he is or how tense the game gets, he's showing off that he doesn't plan on stopping.
He's letting Shiratorizawa's middle blocker know to keep his guard up.
Let's go!
What was that?
Up front!
That's your chance, Ball!
It's too short!
Volleyball is a sport where you can't hold the ball. You only touch it for split seconds.
You must be able to control that moment, as if the ball was actually an extension of your own body. And your body is small. So you'll have to make up for it in other ways.
His body was moving to the right, but he used his left hand.
Oh!
No!
He managed to turn around what could have been a disaster.
Were your damn sneakers glued to the floor!
What are you doing?
You could've gotten that ball!
Amazing.
We pulled it off!
Good job guys!
What?
That's insane!
He's a good boy!
Thank you!
Right now is our chance.
If you get another chance, then take it!
We can do this. Let's go!
That was a nice cover.
Can't you at least see that with a happy face? Geez!
More importantly, Kageyama.
We have another set! Ahead of us!
Yeah.
Oh, oh.
ゆとり思って サボり詰め込んで
ココリ高く生きたいのだ
あとは君次第です
全部君次第
きっと甘い甘いと言われても
違うよ 違う 溶けなされたって
あとは君次第 迷うんじゃない
君次第
ご視聴ありがとうございました
チャンネル登録よろしくお願いします
Thank you.